<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lyrical</string>
    <string name="iceicebaby">
        Alright stop, collaborate and listen\n
        Ice is back with my brand new invention\n
        Something grabs a hold of me tightly\n
        Flow like a harpoon daily and nightly\n
        Will it ever stop? Yo I don\'t know\n
        Turn off the lights and I\'ll glow\n
        To the extreme, I rock a mic like a vandal\n
        Light up a stage and wax a chump like a candle\n
        Dance go rush the speaker that booms\n
        I\'m killing your brain like a poisonous mushroom\n
        Deadly when I play a dope melody\n
        Anything less than the best is a felony\n
        Love it or leave it you better gangway\n
        You better hit bull\'s eye the kid don\'t play\n
        If there was a problem yo I\'ll solve it\n
        Check out the hook while my DJ revolves it\n
        \n
        Now that the party is jumping\n
        With the bass kicked in and the Vegas are pumping\n
        Quick to the point to the point no faking\n
        I\'m cooking MCs like a pound of bacon\n
        Burning them if you ain\'t quick and nimble\n
        I go crazy when I hear a cymbal\n
        And a hi-hat with a souped up tempo\n
        I\'m on a roll and it\'s time to go solo\n
        Rollin\' in my 5.0\n
        With my rag-top down so my hair can blow\n
        The girlies on standby waving just to say hi\n
        Did you stop? No, I just drove by\n
        Kept on pursuing to the next stop\n
        I busted a left and I\'m heading to the next block\n
        The block was dead\n
        Yo so I continued to A1A Beachfront Avenue\n
        Girls were hot wearing less than bikinis\n
        Rockman lovers driving Lamborghinis\n
        Jealous \'cause I\'m out getting mine\n
        Shay with a gauge and Vanilla with a nine\n
        Ready for the chumps on the wall\n
        The chumps acting ill because they\'re full of eight ball\n
        Gunshots rang out like a bell\n
        I grabbed my nine all I heard were shells\n
        Falling on the concrete real fast\n
        Jumped in my car slammed on the gas\n
        Bumper to bumper the avenue\'s packed\n
        I\'m trying to get away before the jackers jack\n
        Police on the scene you know what I mean\n
        They passed me up confronted all the dope fiends\n
        If there was a problem yo I\'ll solve it\n
        Check out the hook while my DJ revolves it\n
        \n
        Take heed \'cause I\'m a lyrical poet\n
        Miami\'s on the scene just in case you didn\'t know it\n
        My town that created all the bass sound\n
        Enough to shake and kick holes in the ground\n
        \'Cause my style\'s like a chemical spill\n
        Feasible rhymes that you can vision and feel\n
        Conducted and formed, this is a hell of a concept\n
        We make it hype and you want to step\n
        With this. Shay plays on the fade\n
        Slice like a ninja, cut like a razor blade\n
        So fast, other DJs say Damn!\n
        If my rhyme was a drug I\'d sell it by the gram\n
        Keep my composure when it\'s time to get loose\n
        Magnetized by the mic while I kick my juice\n
        If there was a problem yo I\'ll solve it\n
        Check out the hook while D-Shay revolves it
    </string>
    <string name="golddigger">
        Cutie the bomb, met her at a beauty salon\n
        With a baby Louis Vuitton under her underarm\n
        She said: I can tell you rock, I can tell by your charm\n
        Far as girls, you got a flock\n
        I can tell by your charm and your arm\n
        But I\'m lookin\' for the one, have you seen her?\n
        My psychic told me she\'ll have a ass like Serena\n
        Trina, Jennifer Lopez, four kids\n
        And I gotta take all they bad asses to ShowBiz?\n
        Okay, get your kids, but then they got their friends\n
        I pulled up in the Benz, they all got up in\n
        We all went to din\' and then I had to pay\n
        If you fuckin\' with this girl, then you better be paid\n
        You know why? It take too much to touch her\n
        From what I heard she got a baby by Busta\n
        My best friend said she used to fuck with Usher\n
        I don\'t care what none of y\'all say, I still love her\n
        \n
        Eighteen years, eighteen years\n
        She got one of your kids, got you for eighteen years\n
        I know somebody payin\' child support for one of his kids\n
        His baby mama car and crib is bigger than his\n
        You will see him on TV any given Sunday\n
        Win the Super Bowl and drive off in a Hyundai\n
        She was supposed to buy your shorty Tyco with your money\n
        She went to the doctor, got lipo with your money\n
        She walkin\' around lookin\' like Michael with your money\n
        Shoulda got that insured, Geico for your money\n
        If you ain\'t no punk\n
        Holla, We want prenup! We want prenup! (Yeah!)\n
        It\'s somethin\' that you need to have\n
        \‘Cause when she leave yo\' ass, she gon\' leave with half\n
        Eighteen years, eighteen years\n
        And on the 18th birthday, he found out it wasn\'t his?\n
        \n
        Now, I ain\'t sayin\' you a gold digger, you got needs\n
        You don\'t want a dude to smoke, but he can\'t buy weed\n
        You go out to eat, he can\'t pay, y\'all can\'t leave\n
        There\'s dishes in the back, he gotta roll up his sleeves\n
        But while y\'all washin\', watch him\n
        He gon\' make it to a Benz out of that Datsun\n
        He got that ambition, baby, look at his eyes\n
        This week he moppin\' floors, next week it\'s the fries\n
        So stick by his side\n
        I know there\'s dudes ballin\', and yeah, that\'s nice\n
        And they gonna keep callin\' and tryin\', but you stay right, girl\n
        And when you get on, he\'ll leave yo\' ass for a white girl
    </string>
    <string name="feels">
        Goddamn, I know you love to make an entrance\n
        Do you like getting paid or getting paid attention?\n
        You mixed the wrong guys with the right intentions
        In the same bed, but it still feel long distance\n
        She\'s looking for a little more consistency\n
        But when you stop looking you gon\' find what\'s meant to be\n
        And honestly, I\'m way too done with the hoes\n
        I cut off all my exes for your x and o\'s\n
        I feel my old flings was just preparing me\n
        When I say I want you, say it back, parakeet\n
        Fly in first-class through the air, Airbnb\n
        I\'m the best you had, you just be comparing me to me\n
        I\'ma \'at\' this at you, if I put you on my phone\n
        And upload it, it\'ll get maximum views\n
        I came through in the clutch with the lipsticks and phones\n
        Wear your fave cologne just to get you alone
    </string>
    <string name="clique">
        I tell a bad bitch do whatever I say\n
        My block behind me, like I\'m coming out the driveway\n
        It\'s grind day, from Friday to next Friday\n
        I been up straight for nine days, I need a spa day (spa day)\n
        Yup, she tryin\' to get me that poon-tang\n
        I might let my crew bang, my crew deeper than Wu-Tang\n
        I\'m rollin\' with&#8230; fuck I\'m saying? Girl, you know my crew name\n
        You know 2 Chainz? Scrrr!\n
        I\'m pullin\' up in that Bruce Wayne\n
        But I\'m the fuckin\' villain\n
        Man, they kneelin\' when I\'m walking in the buildin\'\n
        Freaky women I be feelin\' from the bank accounts I\'m fillin\'\n
        What a feelin\'! Ah man, they gotta be\n
        Young player from the D\n
        That\'s killing everything that he see for the dough\n
        \n
        Yeah, I\'m talkin\' Ye, yeah, I\'m talkin\' Rih\n
        Yeah, I\'m talkin\' B, nigga, I\'m talkin\' me\n
        Yeah, I\'m talkin\' bossy, I ain\'t talkin\' Kelis\n
        Your money too short, you can\'t be talking to me\n
        Yeah, I\'m talkin\' LeBron, we ball in our family tree\n
        G.O.O.D. Music drug-dealing cousin\n
        Ain\'t nothin\' fuckin\' with we, me\n
        Turn that 62 to 125, 125 to a 250\n
        250 to a half a million, ain\'t nothin\' nobody can do with me\n
        Now, who with me? ¡Vámonos! Call me Hov or Jefe\n
        Translation: I\'m the shit, least that what my neck say\n
        Least that what my check say, lost my homie for a decade\n
        Nigga down for like 12 years\n
        Ain\'t hug his son since the second grade\n
        Uh, he never told—who he gonna tell?\n
        We top of the totem pole\n
        It\'s the Dream Team meets the Supreme Team\n
        And all our eyes green, it only means one thing\n
        You ain\'t fuckin\' with the clique\n
        \n
        Break records at Louis, ate breakfast at Gucci\n
        My girl a superstar all from a home movie\n
        Bow on our arrival, the un-American idols\n
        What niggas did in Paris, got \'em hangin\' off the Eiffel\n
        Yeah, I\'m talkin\' business, we talkin\' CIA\n
        I\'m talkin\' George Tenet, I seen him the other day\n
        He asked me about my Maybach, think he had the same\n
        Except mine tinted and his might have been rented\n
        You know, white people get money, don\'t spend it\n
        Or maybe they get money, buy a business\n
        I rather buy 80 gold chains and go ign\'ant\n
        I know Spike Lee gon\' kill me, but let me finish\n
        Blame it on the pigment, we livin\' no limits\n
        Them gold Master P ceilings was just a figment\n
        Of our imagination, MTV cribs\n
        Now I\'m lookin\' at a crib right next to where TC lives\n
        That\'s Tom Cruise, whatever she accuse\n
        He wasn\'t really drunk, he just had a frew brews\n
        Pass the refreshments, a cool, cool beverage\n
        Everything I do need a news crew\'s presence\n
        Speedboat swerve, homie, watch out for the waves\n
        I\'m way too black to burn from sunrays\n
        So I just meditate at the home in Pompeii\n
        About how I could build a new Rome in one day\n
        Every time I\'m in Vegas they screamin\' like he\'s Elvis\n
        But I just wanna design hotels and nail it\n
        Shit is real, got me feelin\' Israelian\n
        Like Bar Refaeli, or Gisele—no, that\'s Brazilian\n
        Went through, deep depression when my mama passed\n
        Suicide, what kinda talk is that?\n
        But I been talkin\' to God for so long\n
        That if you look at my life I guess he\'s talkin\' back\n
        Fuckin\' with my clique
    </string>
    <string name="themotto">
        I\'m the fuckin\' man, y\'all don\'t get it, do ya?\n
        Type of money, everybody acting like they knew ya\n
        Go Uptown, New York City, bitch\n
        Them Spanish girls love me like I\'m Aventura\n
        Tell Uncle Luke I\'m out in Miami, too\n
        Clubbing hard, fucking women, there ain\'t much to do\n
        Wrist bling, got a condo up in Biscayne\n
        Still getting brain from a thang, ain\'t shit changed\n
        How you feel, how you feel, how you feel?\n
        25, sitting on 25 mill, uh\n
        I\'m in the building and I\'m feeling myself\n
        Rest in peace, Mac Dre, I\'m-a do it for the Bay\n
        Okay, getting paid, we\'ll holler whenever that stop\n
        My team good, we don\'t really need a mascot\n
        Tell Tune, Light one, pass it like a relay\n
        YMCMB, you niggas more YMCA\n
        Me, Franny, and Mally Mall at the crib-o\n
        Shout goes out to Niko, J and Chubbs, shouts to Gibbo\n
        We got Santa Margherita by the liter\n
        She know even if I\'m fucking with her, I don\'t really need her\n
        Aww, that\'s how you feel, man? That\'s really how you feel?\n
        Cause the pimpin ice cold, all these bitches wanna chill\n
        I mean maybe she won\'t but then again maybe she will\n
        I can almost guarantee she know the deal, real nigga, what\'s up?\n
        \n
        One&#8230;time? Fuck one time\n
        I\'m calling niggas out like the umpire\n
        Seven&#8230;grams in the blunt\n
        Almost drowned in her pussy so I swam to her butt\n
        It\'s Eastside, we in this bitch\n
        Wish a nigga would, like a tree in this bitch\n
        And if a leaf fall put some weed in that bitch\n
        That\'s my MO, add a B to that shit\n
        I\'m fucked up, tore down\n
        I\'m twisted: door knob\n
        Talk stupid? Off with your head!\n
        Nigga, money talks, and Mr. Ed, yeah\n
        I\'m so Young Money\n
        Got a drum on the gun, Energizer bunny\n
        Funny how honey ain\'t sweet like sugar\n
        Ain\'t shit sweet? Niggas on the street like hookers\n
        I tongue kiss her other tongue\n
        Skeet skeet skeet: water gun\n
        Oh my God, Becky, look at her butt! Tunechi\n
        \n
        T-Raww, skinny nigga, big balls\n
        Fuck around and get dragged: RuPaul\n
        You funny little nigga, Duval\n
        Out of this world, Total Recall\n
        Call a bitch, ride dick like a seesaw\n
        Sorta like a donkey, act a ass nigga hee-haw\n
        Ridin round in the \'rarri wit the top off\n
        While you in the window, man I’m probably on my next car\n
        Aight, mighty duck with the ice on\n
        Real LA nigga, chucks with the gun drawn\n
        Drawing on your face you\'re a clown jack in the box\n
        Boy that\'s your bop, she my new pum pum star\n
        Stars in the back, them my homies, they don\'t act\n
        Acting brand new, fuck her never call her back\n
        Matt Forte got the bitch running back\n
        Damn, That\'s the motto you don\'t know it\'s like that
    </string>
    <string name="youalreadyknow">
        Let it go, get rolled, I just can\'t hold\n
        Back and forth \'cause I\'m the girl with soul\n
        Ain\'t controlling effects, so what the heck\n
        Rock the discotheque \'cause this groove is up next\n
        Tease on the camera, freeze while I animate\n
        I\'m no amateur, I\'ma laminate\n
        I\'ma assassinate all the imitates\n
        Then I\'ma take a break, and meditate\n
        Hmm, let me think about it\n
        Put my little noodle on the problem, then I drink about it\n
        Drink a little, swig a little, sip a little, spill a little\n
        Feel a little loopy when I get a little tipsy\n
        Beez got me feeling like a gypsy\n
        Smoking on a hookah got me feeling like a hippie, trippy\n
        Gone for a minute and you missed me\n
        Now Fergie back with a bag full of tricksies, what\n
        \n
        Yo, ayo, let it go, let\'s go\n
        I keep a bar like Esco\n
        I wanna ball, where the nets go?\n
        I\'m on stage, you can stand where the guests go\n
        Bitches is my sons, they don\'t wanna leave the nest, though\n
        They like, aw, where the ref go?\n
        I-I got these hoes scared to pass, I got that intercept flow\n
        I made a movie like Seth Rog\'\n
        And since I came in the game, they careers on death row\n
        Damn, they ain\'t seen young Nicki in a week\n
        Five shows, made three millie in a week\n
        You are now looking at the best, the elite\n
        Too bad you can\'t go and invest in them critiques\n
        I\'m thick and petite, tell \'em quick, pick a seat\n
        I pull up in the Ghost, no sheets, trick or treat\n
        I know they on E, but I don\'t give a F, though\n
        Bad attitude, but my pussy is the best, though\n
        \n
        Come get some, you little bums\n
        Dudes want the cake, but they can\'t get a crumb\n
        From the original, sexual, visual dope chick and all that good shit\n
        Charismatic when I\'m at it\n
        When I add it up, I\'m mathematic, baby\n
        Top game, I\'m out the attic\n
        There you have it, no dramatics, hold the static\n
        Pose for the camera, daddy, I\'m vogueing\n
        Baby, I\'m glamorous, and I\'m folding\n
        Grammys and AMAs, I\'m holding\n
        Amazing the way I keep shit frozen\n
        Cool, that\'s true, got new shoes and a new attitude\n
        Got my hair did, got a new hairdo\n
        Come and see me at a venue near you
    </string>
    <string name="mobounce">
        Bounce like a motherfuckin\' \'64, sick flow\n
        Slick talk, spittin\' that Crisco\n
        Drop that shit like a cholo at the dub show\n
        Can you hit the switch and pick it up and let the world know?\n
        Homie, if you\'re broke, oh, no you don\'t deserve hoes\n
        All these fake boulders only gettin\' on my nerves though\n
        I just cracked a 40, now I\'m sippin\' out the straw slow\n
        Little bit of ratchet, little boujee, you should all know\n
        Everybody got opinions, yeah, like assholes\n
        You ain\'t gotta worry \'bout those, \'cause they assholes\n
        We just came to party, party, party, what you came for?\n
        Make, make the neighborhood bounce to this\n
        \n
        Bounce that ass, bounce that ass, yeah, bounce it\n
        Puff the lah or get high off the contact\n
        Call the law, we gon\' make sure we come back\n
        Fallin\' off, we ain\'t ever been about that\n
        Hundred spokes spinnin\' on a chrome rim\n
        I got a feelin\' that tonight we gon\' be goin\' in\n
        I\'m with a few bad bitches and some grown men\n
        With the ice so cold, I feel like I\'m Snowden\n
        I feel like I\'m rollin\', but the whole place geeked up\n
        It\'s gettin\' hot in here, down to my wife beater\n
        But you ain\'t gotta worry, we ain\'t dangerous\n
        We came up\n
        Make, make the neighborhood bounce to this
    </string>
    <string name="logic">
        Ayo, ayo, Wu-Tang forever, who rhyme better?\n
        We too clever, the boom bap\'s back, harder than ever\n
        R.I.P. O.D.B, comin\' through like Killa Bee\n
        Ever since I heard Enter the 36 in \'93\n
        You cannot defeat my Wu-Tang style, I leave \'em all dismembered\n
        Fuck a mumble rap, that shit won\'t never be remembered\n
        Not even a contender, no, pretender, best surrender\n
        My agenda is killin\' shit, they feelin\' this (Sinatra)\n
        Yeah, we live and thorough\n
        Assassinatin\' every single muthafuckin\' borough\n
        From Staten to Brooklyn to Queens, the Bronx and Harlem\n
        All the way to Maryland, yeah, we comin\' for all \'em\n
        Bobby Tarantino to the Digital\n
        My shit is pivotal, smokin\' chronic, no medicinal\n
        Who you know assemble the Clan like Voltron?\n
        The one and only Logic, the God, the don, I\'m gone
    </string>
    <string name="ghostfacekillah">
        Yo, yo, yo, yo, kaboom!\n
        Guess who stepped in the room\n
        It\'s Ghostface, gold plates, old truths, more cake\n
        Intelligent brothers with nine hoods, movin\' snowflakes\n
        Guillotine your head, last scene in the showcase\n
        Push weight, this Colgate, tre-eights and old gates\n
        Exfoliate those we most hate, we don\'t associate\n
        We wear robes that you can\'t even pronunciate\n
        We eat foods where you can\'t even pronounce you ate\n
        Cribs where the floor just rises up and rotates\n
        Locations low-key, can\'t even locate\n
        Twin nina sisters with the beam, we all soulmates\n
        Team makin\' us so much cream, we bought gold plates
    </string>
    <string name="raekwon">
        Yo, mountains of haze in the crib of my blades\n
        It gets messy underneath the dresser, the gauge\n
        57 MB, yo, metallic green, seats is piped off\n
        Seize \'em old tracks, unite through \'em\n
        The kitchen is my palace, get your dance on\n
        While we just levitate with trees, get your branch on\n
        I\'m known to wil\' out, put the cams on\n
        Jewels down, the sets dip, my gems got grams on\n
        A specialist when I\'m bakin\'\n
        Rhymes be comin\' out, we makin\'\n
        We challengin\' these chumps for lumps\n
        Here\'s the statement—stop hatin\'\n
        The crew is all about gettin\' this cake in\n
        You know about me, you relatin\'
    </string>
    <string name="rza">
        The enigma, the stigmas that the RZA and the GZA\n
        Both lyrical prolific, fixtures of rap scriptures\n
        Mixtures of hipsters, weed smokers, and beer drinkers\n
        Prince and the Pauper, spiritual clear-thinkers\n
        Cake in the oven, Superbad like McLovin\n
        Huggin\' all four boroughs, puffin\' herb with my cousin\n
        Academically speaking, rap vocabulary\'s weakenin\'\n
        I felt it comin\' like The Weeknd when these starboys start tweakin\'\n
        Sporadic pill-poppin\' of OxyContin\n
        III-gotten sexual intercourse make shorty wop feel rotten\n
        The travesty-tapestry of microphone mastery has been refuted\n
        Diluted, broken down to a catastrophe\n
        But cats still get the trophy, hit y\'all with that Okie-dokie\n
        Burt Reynolds, Bandit, goddamnit\n
        Where the fuck is Smokey Bear when you need one?\n
        I got a light-beam gun\n
        I\'ll blast a hole in your chest that you can\'t bleed from\n
        But you\'ll die through iniquity, plus stupidity of that trickery\n
        My verse got it hot up in here, not the humidity\n
        You can never get rid of me, step back and consider me\n
        Wu Killa Bee, but I\'m not big on bigotry
    </string>
    <string name="methodman">
        Old school on this track, I feel invincible\n
        This new school ain\'t really got rules and lack the principles\n
        Got more clowns than the Motown, they puttin\' critical\n
        The gun, Smokey Robinson, you need a Miracle\n
        Go back, homie, back when rappers used to be lyrical\n
        When nine out of ten of his friends used to be criminals\n
        The stats, homie, all these killas usin\' subliminals\n
        Y\'all don\'t even smile in your pictures, you dudes is miserable\n
        Witty unpredictable torture over your physical\n
        Struggle bar, used to pour water over the cereal\n
        Another bar, reppin\' my squad, not individual\n
        But one Nation under God, that\'s indivisible\n
        My time critical, hands off I\'m digital\n
        Me and my Ladybug, back when the planet was Digable\n
        I\'m cool like that, my cash rule like that\n
        I\'m classic, Patti LaBelle, Voulez Vous like that, come on
    </string>
    <string name="inspectahdeck">
        It\'s only Logic, we got \'em mobbin\' in the mosh pit\n
        Fifth Brother, INS hotter than the tropics\n
        The hot shit I drop quick\n
        Major player, watch my stock lift\n
        Razor-blade sharpness regardless to whom or what\n
        Sound boy, turn that music up\n
        Naysayer, you ain\'t even got a clue what\'s up\n
        Deadly melody, the sickness, the remedy\n
        Everything circulate back around eventually\n
        Witty unpredictable, talent all-natural\n
        Gain, Wu-Tang pumpin\' through your veins\n
        Twenty-five years, still more of the same\n
        The flow like water with the boilin\' flame\n
        INS, your highness, they callin\' my name\n
        Boy, I wet the scene similar to fallin\' rain\n
        In our own lane, y\'all soundin\' all the same\n
        Tell \'em Wu-Tang is on your brain
    </string>
    <string name="cappadonna">
        Survival of the fittest be cold days with no money\n
        They don\'t want me with stacks, they better take it from me\n
        You know the currency gone soon as you break a twenty\n
        So I ain\'t down if you ain\'t talkin\' that band language\n
        Dear Lord, I\'m tryna buy me a train with it\n
        An airplane, see me flyin\' to Spain with it\n
        But money don\'t make me, and I ain\'t gonna change with it\n
        I\'m in the hood, lookin\' good, the way I came with it\n
        Do it for the Cs, they understood the game with it\n
        We gave birth when we understood the pain with it\n
        When we create wars, everybody is a gangbanger\n
        We killin\' each other, but we all got the same anger\n
        Never go against the grain, homie, that\'s hateful\n
        Another day in the life for us to be grateful\n
        Spread love, homie, yeah, get a plateful\n
        It\'s better to stay full, so let\'s make moves\n
        I know your momma told you that I was a great dude\n
        These dirty-ass cops, they kill and rape you\n
        On some Jason shit, might Crystal in the Lake you\n
        What? What, what? They might Crystal in the Lake you
    </string>
    <string name="jackpotscottywotty">
        Boom bap blast\'ll blow your sleeves off\n
        Our Flashback Jacks are somethin\' to feed off\n
        Smoke and roast ya, the No. 9 Potion\n
        Pull that shit, son, we open the ocean\n
        Who gives a fuck who\'s snortin\' and drinkin\' and smokin\'?\n
        You get killed for jokin\', everybody\'s hopin\'\n
        That\'s another level of emotion\n
        Food stamps niggas doin\' grocery\n
        Police wanna grope me\n
        Perp walk, then nigga street-talk\n
        We bury niggas in sea salt\n
        I carry the torch where I leave off\n
        I\'m givin\' bitches somethin\' to breathe on\n
        I rip off a shoulder to lean on\n
        It\'s fair game, it\'s two in a lane, she took two trains\n
        And none of my rhymes are two and the same\n
        Nigga get cooked on a open flame\n
        I\'m a hillbilly, Park Hill-trained
    </string>
    <string name="ugod">
        My rhyme starts riots in the mountains\n
        Thirty-six million and countin\'\n
        The harder they come, the harder I go\n
        Loosen up my arms, can I get comfortable?\n
        Stay on my tip-toes, old-school Wu beat\n
        This is a flip-phone, dude, your slips showin\'\n
        Where I come from it stays snowin\'\n
        The grammar is raw, I\'m slammin\' the door\n
        Beez bang bong in your jaw\n
        I hit \'em in the head with the hammer of Thor\n
        Stars and bars, makes me a general\n
        Anything less, makes me a criminal\n
        Gotta dig deep for these Wu-Tang minerals
    </string>
    <string name="mastakilla">
        G.O.D., shadowbox with the L.O.G.I.C\n
        On the count of three, Wu-Tang\n
        First, master your breathin\'\n
        I\'m mental ass-whoopin\', I\'m teachin\' when I\'m speakin\'\n
        I\'m a champion from Brooklyn\n
        I\'m movin\' super-ninjas and Shaolin executioners\n
        Avenger, a righteous defender\n
        Grandmaster from the 36th Chamber\n
        Toad style is mentally strong, so strengthen your arms\n
        To hold my microphone you need iron palms\n
        Remain calm, Jamel Irief\n
        Wise chief, Wu-Tang poison clansman from the east, yeah
    </string>
    <string name="gza">
        Enter a world of a universal mind of one kind\n
        A thick swarm of words that\'s expressed in one rhyme\n
        Food for thought, impossible sliders with the seasoning Regardless, I speak logic—clear reasoning\n
        The uncivilized, get the mineral lines, quartz\n
        Self-directed, calculated, controlled thoughts\n
        A point-of-view of the thinkers\n
        Monumental architecture, amazing as the Incas
    </string>
</resources>
